

# **Shaival Patel**

23/Purnanand soc. B/H Savan soc. Bhaduatnagar, Po-Ghodasar Ahmedabad-380050 E-mail: shaival009@gmail.com

**Phone:** 9725628720

## **OBJECTIVE**

A quantity surveyor with more than five years of experience in cost control and analysis, billing and estimation, project procurement and management, contract management and preparation of contract documents in industrial projects. Secure a responsible career opportunity to fully utilize my training and skills, while making a significant contribution to the success of the company.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

# S3M DESIGN CONSULTANTS LLP

17/11/2020 — Present

### **COST & PROCUREMENT ENGINEER**

- Conducting detail calculation of quantities and estimation of project.
- Preparing contract document and conduction tendering process.
- Checking contractor's bills and preparing certificate of payment.
- Observing current market trends and update current rates regularly
- Preparing rate analysis.
- Apart from this, part of infrastructure designing work.

# M/s Vipul K Patel

01/07/2016 — 14/11/2020

Billing and Planning Engineer

- Preparation of client bills to approval with clients.
- Preparation of contractor's bill.
- Reconciliation of free issue material.
- Analysis of tender from market, understand the tender conditions and submit with best competitive rates.
- Preparation of dpr, wpr & fpr for various projects.
- List down daily requirement from all the sites and plan accordingly.
- Progress chart of projects.

### **EDUCATION**

# Masters in Civil Engineering

September 2014 — July 2016

GTU(BVM engineering college, Vallabh Vidyanagar)

# **Bachelor of Civil Engineering**

August 2010 — May 2010

GTU(Vishwakarma Government Engineering College)

# LIST OF PROJECTS

### S3m Design Consultants LLP

Major Projects

1) Aegios Polyfilms Private Limited - Preparation of BOQ & Bid documents for Civil, Architectural & Infrastructure works. Preparation of TCS & QCS.

Shaival Patel

- 2) IFFCO Nano Fertilizer Expansion Project, Kalol Preparation of PEB Bid, BOQ & Bid documents for Civil, Architectural & Infrastructure works. Preparation of TCS & QCS.
- 3) IFFCO Nano Fertilizer Project, Aonla & Phulpur Revision of Civil, Architectural & Infrastructure works BOQ due major change and increase in scope of work.
- 4) Adani Wilmar, Gohana Preparation of Civil, Architectural & Infrastructure works BOQ.
- 5) Bill checking for IFFCO Aonla, Phulpur, Kalol & Kalol expansion.
- 6) Augmentation of Storm Water drain, Adani Mundra Design of storm water drain, preparation of DBR & BOQ for civil & Mechanical works.

### M/S Vipul K Patel

# Major Projects

- 1) Multipurpose Godown at Adani Port, Dahej Site supervisor and QA/QC work.
- 2) Development of Yard at Adani Port, Dahej Execution and Billing Work
- 3) Civil, Architectural and Infrastructure work at Deepak Fertilizer Private Limited, Suva, Dahej. Billing & Planning Engineer
- 4) Civil, Architectural and Infrastructure work at ICA Pidilite, Jambusar, Bharuch. Billing & Planning Engineer
- 5) Civil and Infrastructure work at Remi Metals, Jagadia, Bharuch. Biiling & Planning Engineer
- 6) Civil and Infrasture work at Welspun corporation at Welspun, Bhopal MAnaging Project as well as Billing.

### **SKILLS**

#### **General Skills**

Computer Proficiency
Communication Skill
Leadership Experience
Problem Solving Abilities

#### Software Skills

Microsoft Excel Microsoft Word AutoCAD STAADPro ETABS

# **LANGUAGE**

English Hindi Gujarati

### **REFERENCES**

1) Hiten Shah Managing Partner at S3m Design Consultsnts LLP Co. No. 9825411671

2) Vipul Patel Owner at M/s Vipul K Patel Co. No. 9099036650

Shaival Patel